我们 是水晶
♪ We ♪ are the crystal
战士
♪ gems
我们总能拯救世界
♪ we'll always save the day
如果你认为我们不行
♪ and if you think we can't, ♪
我们总能找到方法
♪ we'll always find a way
这就是为什么这个世界
♪ that's why the people
的人
♪ of this world
相信
♪ believe in
石榴
♪ Garnet
紫晶
♪ Amethyst
和珍珠
♪ and Pearl
和史蒂文!
and Steven!
好好
拉尔斯
欢迎关注微博@UUU字幕组，获取最新熟肉信息！
出品
UUU字幕组
翻译
presisco
校对
Husky
特效
presisco
压制
那么 怎么样?
So how is it?
说实话 但也不要太坦诚
Be honest but not too honest.
南瓜做的面包!
It's pumpkin bread!
南瓜似的外形 就像个南瓜!
And it's pumpkin-shaped like a pumpkin!
这么好的点子怎么从没有人想到过!
This is the best idea anybody has ever had!
听到没? 我就说
See? I told you.
这很赞
It's really good.
当然史蒂文会喜欢
Of course Steven likes it.
他什么都喜欢
He likes everything.
拉尔斯 这是你做的吗?
Lars did you make this?
不!
No!
其实 是的 没什么大不了的
Well yes but it's no big deal.
说出秘密了吧 拉尔斯
Secret's out Lars.
感觉良好 不是吗?
Feels good doesn't it?
啊 别说了
Ah stop.
哦 这真是棒极了!
Oh this is amazing!
你是怎么让它有南瓜的外形的?
How'd you get it to look like a pumpkin?
我只是做了七个小的新月形的蛋糕
I just made seven small crescent-shaped cakes
然后用奶油芝士糖霜让它们定型
and used cream-cheese icing to hold them together.
只要不是智障和手残都能完成
Anyone with two hands and half a brain could do it.
还有 你知道的 一份菜谱
And you know a recipe.
这是他表达谢意的方式
That's his way of saying thanks.
我知道 我懂拉尔斯语
I know. I speak Lars.
巴-巴-巴-巴克·杜威!
B-B-B-Buck Dewey!
嗨 巴克
Hi Buck.
嘿 史蒂文
Hey Steven.
嘿 甜甜圈伙计们
Hey doughnut kids.
嗨 巴克 怎么样?
Hi Buck what's up?
一切还好吗? 要什么?
How's it going? What'll it be?
我想要...你们 来吃晚饭
I want to order...you to come to dinner.
我 珍妮 还有酸奶油要搞个家常聚餐
Me Jenny and Sour Cream are having a potluck.
你懂的 像家长搞的那种
You know like parents do.
只不过是我们主持
Except we'll be doing it.
你们三个都该来看看
All three of you should come.
你们得带上点食物
You should bring some food
因为家常聚餐就是这样
because that's what you do at a potluck.
非常有趣
It's so funny.
确实很有趣 巴克!
That is funny Buck!
听起来非常棒 酷炸天
It sounds great. Super cool.
等不及了 牛逼闪闪
Can't wait. Bingo bongo.
酷
Cool.
"牛逼闪闪"?
"Bingo bongo"?
我是从哪听到的?
Where did I even learn that?
没错!
Yeah!
牛逼闪闪!
Bingo bongo!
这会非常棒的
This is gonna be great.
嘿 没错 这非常好
Hey yeah this is perfect.
你可能不信我们对你的手艺的评价
You won't believe us when we say we like your cooking
但如果是巴克的话你肯定会信的
but you'll have to believe it when it's coming from Buck.
呃 拉尔斯?
Uh Lars?
我才不去
I'm not going.
什么?! 你刚刚收到的酷小子们的派对邀请啊!
What?! You just got invited to a party with the cool kids!
这不是你一直想要的吗?
Isn't that what you've always wanted?
就算说有人不该去的话 那也是我
If anyone shouldn't go it's me
但他们了解你
but they know you.
他们喜欢你!
They like you!
不 没人了解我
Nah-unh. Nobody knows me.
而且没人知道我会烘焙
And nobody knows I can bake.
不过 我知道 他也知道啊
Well I do and he does.
没错 拉尔斯 你应该把这次作为你的盛大首秀
Yeah Lars you should make this your big debut.
那好吧 不过必须得做到完美
Well...then it has to be perfect.
做个派怎么样?
How about a pie?
不行
No.
呃 热烤阿拉斯加呢?
Uh baked Alaska?
那会显得我太努力
It might look like I'm trying too hard.
没错 某种奶油夹心的甜点
Yeah something cream-filled.
烘面包? 煎饼卷?
A bundt? A cannoli?
或者牛角饼干?
Maybe some rugelach?
没法决定啊!
I don't know!
也许我们可以做个蛋糕 画上你的脸
Maybe we could make a cake with your face on it.
这是个好主意!
That's a great idea!
你应该做个能代表你的东西
You should make something that represents you.
秘密食谱
Secret cookbook.
也许这个能行
Maybe this'll work.
我吃这个长大的
I used to eat this as a kid all the time.
喔 什么是乌比?
Wow. What's...uby?
叫乌贝
It's ube.
那是什么?
What's that?
呃 就是 你懂的 就像甜的土豆
Uh like you know it's like a sweet potato.
土豆可以是甜的?
Potatoes can be sweet?
我是说 严格来讲其实是山药
I mean it's technically a yam.
-山药?-这个听起来太完美了!
Yams?! This sounds perfect!
做好了
It's done.
所以 怎么样?
So how is it?
真是...好极了!
It's...Amazing!
非常好吃
This is delicious.
你真是个出色的烘焙师 拉尔斯
You're an amazing baker Lars.
这个 没错 我当然是啦
Well yeah of course I am.
对不起 拉尔斯 这真的非常好吃
Sorry Lars. It's really good.
我想我可以相信你的话
Guess I have to take your word for it.
我要出发为派对进行点准备了
I'm gonna head out and get my stuff for the party.
就这样吧! 居然真成了!
This is it! It's all happening!
拉尔斯和酷小子们!
Lars and the cool kids!
聚会见!
See ya there!
再见 莎蒂
Bye Sadie.
一切都那么美好
Everything is so good.
没错 有点过头了
Yeah too good.
你是什么意思?
What do you mean?
呃 算了
Uh never mind.
嗷 别啊
Aw come on.
你什么都可以告诉我
You can tell me anything.
我还用过你的身体呢
I spent a day in your body.
不是什么大事 不要管了
It's nothing. Forget about it.
分享你的感受
Open up about your feelings.
我不是担心蛋糕
I'm not worried about the cake.
蛋糕肯定非常好
The cake is gonna rule.
我是担心带蛋糕去这件事
I'm worried about showing up with a cake.
什么意思?
What do you mean?
我不想告诉大家我会烘焙是有原因的
There's a reason I don't like telling anybody I like baking.
什么原因呢?
And what's that?
因为烘焙很搓 史蒂文!
Because it's lame Steven!
要是参加这个聚会时
If I show up to this party
我带着这个奇怪的紫色蛋糕和莎蒂的话
with my family's weird purple cake and with Sadie
所有人都会知道我喜欢烘焙
everybody's gonna know I love baking
而且所有人都会知道我喜欢...
and everybody's gonna know I love...
这次家常聚会的讽刺意义就没了
This isn't gonna be an ironic potluck.
而是会变成
It's gonna be like
家庭 情侣 邻居 真正的家常聚会
family couple neighbor actual potluck
然后我在那儿 "牛逼闪闪"的
and I'm gonna be there being all bingo bongo.
那些是你的朋友
These are your friends.
他们想要你去
They want you to come.
所以他们才邀请你--
That's why they invited you--
就是为了更了解你
so they'll get to know you better.
如果他们喜欢你 那很好
If they like you they like you.
如果他们不喜欢 那是他们的损失
If they don't then it's their loss.
对吧?
Right?
说的很透彻
That's pretty smart.
你什么时候变得这么成熟了?
When did you get so mature?
可能在学习如何召唤我的护盾
Somewhere in between learning to summon my shield
与发现我妈是个战犯之间吧
and finding out my mom is a war criminal.
好吧! 我会去的
Okay! I'll do it.
拉尔斯! 这一定会很棒的!
Lars! It's going to go so good!
我得出发准备自己的东西了
I got to get going and make my thing
咱们聚会时再见 可以?
but I'll see you there right?
可以
Yeah.
好 之后见
Yeah I'll see you.
嘿 伙计
Hey man.
谁这么好运?
Who's feeling lucky?
我的天 真是个盛宴
My my. What a feast.
我带了苏打水
I brought the soda.
我带了披萨
I brought the pizza.
我带了很多种水果
I brought the assorted fruit.
我等不及拉尔斯来这儿了
I can't wait for Lars to get here.
他做了个--等等 我不能告诉你们
He made a--wait wait I shouldn't tell you.
是个惊喜
It's a surprise.
那个拉尔斯总是充满了惊喜
That Lars is full of surprises.
几天前 他说了句话
The other day he did this thing.
是什么来着? "牛逼闪闪"
What was it? Bingo bongo.
真是酷出了新境界
It was transcendent.
真有创意
That is so creative.
牛逼闪闪
Bingo bongo.
他来了!
That's him!
哦 莎蒂
Oh Sadie.
拉尔斯呢?
Where's Lars?
他还没到吗?
He's not here yet?
他可能还在准备蛋糕
He's probably still working on the cake.
毕竟这可是他乌贝的首秀
This is his ube debut after all.
进来吧?
Why don't you come on in?
哦 呃...
Oh uh...
我喜欢奶酪
I love me some cheese.
你和你花哨的奶酪盘
You and your fancy cheese plates.
哦 嘿 是甜甜圈女孩
Oh hey it's doughnut girl.
大家 这位是莎蒂
Everybody this is Sadie.
呃 嗨 我是拉尔斯的 朋友
Uh hi. I'm Lars'friend.
你好 我是珍妮
What's up? I'm Jenny.
-再次欢迎-我是酸奶油
-Hey again.-I'm Sour Cream.
欢迎来到我家!
Welcome to my house!
那么 告诉我们 莎蒂
So tell us Sadie
你带了什么到我们超级酷的家常聚会?
what did you bring to our very cool potluck?
不好意思 我没带任何食物
Sorry I didn't bring any food.
就只有这些纸碟子
Just these paper plates.
但是 呃 这是给拉尔斯的东西准备的
It's just uh they're for Lars'thing
但是他都没来
and he's not even here.
所以说 我看来得回--
Actually I probably should just show myself--
你带了碟子?
Did you say plates?
万岁!
Hooray!
这样我就不用洗盘子了!
Now I don't have to do the dishes.
喔 没想到还会有人为了纸碟子激动
Wow I never thought anyone could get excited over paper plates.
盘子确实是可降解的就是了
I guess they are biodegradable.
我还是很担心拉尔斯
But I'm still worried about Lars.
我会去找他的 你不要担心
I'll go find him. Don't you worry about it.
玩的愉快
Hang out have fun.
你可以坐在豆袋上
You can sit on the bean bag.
对 那个豆袋可叼了
Yeah that bean bag is sick.
你一定要试试
You got to try it.
哦 好吧
Oh all right.
谁能想到?
What do you know?
很合适
I fit.
就说嘛
Told ya.
我很快会带着拉尔斯回来的
I'll be right back with Lars.
他会在哪呢?
Now where could he be?
拉-啊-啊-啊-啊-啊-啊-尔斯!
La-a-a-a-a-a-rs!
拉尔斯!
Lars!
如果有什么办法能联系到他就好了
If only there was some way to contact him
用心灵感应
with my mind.
哦 等下 用手机就行!
Oh wait or with my phone!
这里是拉尔斯 请留言
This is Lars. Leave a message.
拉-啊-啊-啊-啊-尔斯!
La-a-a-a-a-rs!
我是说 拉尔斯 嗨
I mean Lars hi.
我是史蒂文
This is Steven.
呃 我只是在想你在哪
Uh I was just wondering where you were.
家常聚会进行的非常顺利
The potluck is going really great.
所有人都非常愉快
Everyone's having a nice time
我们都非常希望你能参与进来
and we're all excited for you to come join the fun.
或许我只是错过了你
Or maybe I just missed you
而你已经回到聚会了...
and you're already back at the party...
...而那声音是你和大家在享受音乐
...and that's the sound of you enjoying music with all our friends.
又或许你决定不走进门
Or maybe you decided not to go inside.
也-也没关系
Th-That's okay though.
我想我们之后再见了
Guess I'll see you later.
♪披萨 聚会
♪ Pizza potluck ♪
♪家常 聚会
♪ Potluck potluck ♪
♪聚会
♪ Potluck ♪
很好!
All right!
很不错! 嘿 结尾很好 没错!
Nice! Hey nice ending. Yeah whoo!
没错 莎蒂 很好听
Yeah Sadie. That was fresh.
哦 嘿 是史蒂文
Oh hey it's Steven.
嘿 史蒂文 我们之前玩的非常的愉快
Hey Steven we've been having such a blast over here.
你找到拉尔斯了吗?
Did you find Lars?
呃 没错
Uh yeah.
他今天晚上来不了
he can't make it tonight.
发生了点事
Something came up.
啊 真扫兴啊?
Ah bummer huh?
这样 没关系啦
Well that's okay.
我们接着演奏吧
Let's keep playing music.
-正点-没错!
-Right on.-Yeah!
-再见 伙计们-之后见-再见 伙计们
-Bye guys.-See ya.-Bye guys.
之后见 伙计们
Later guys.
那么 他决定不来了?
So he decided not to come huh?
实际上...
Actually...
嗷 天哪 拉尔斯
Aw geez. Lars.
或许我们之前该更努力劝他的
Maybe we should've tried harder to get him to come.
我想是的
Guess so.
他是那么想融入到他们中
He wants to be in with them so much.
真是有趣
It's funny.
我没想过我会是和他们一起玩的那个
I never thought I'd be the one hanging out with them.
你懂 他们挺酷的
You know they really are cool.
不是拉尔斯想象的那种酷
Like not like he thinks
而是-而是那种很随和的人
but like--like they're actually cool people.
他不去尝试的话他又怎么能知道呢?
How's he going to realize that if he doesn't give them a chance?
我真希望我能强制他高兴
I wish I could just force him to be happy.
哦 不
Oh no.
我听起来跟我妈一样
I sound like my mother.
我也许该先搞好自己的烂摊子 而不是操心他的
Maybe I should be trying to fix my life instead of his.
牛逼闪闪
Bingo bongo.
晚安 史蒂文
Goodnight Steven.
晚安 莎蒂
Goodnight Sadie.